Generated by ai-sub version: 0.0.7
Config: (
"rpm": 5,
"tpm": 250000,
"model": "gemini-2.5-pro",
"thinking_budget": 32768,
"max_subtitle_chars": 50,
"num_processing_threads": 4,
"num_upload_threads": 4,
"split_seconds": 180,
"start_offset_min": 0
)
Prompt Template: You are an expert subtitling and transcription AI. Your primary task is to generate precise, contextually rich English and Japanese subtitles for the provided video content.
**Key Principles & Requirements:**
1.  **TIMING PRECISION (ABSOLUTE HIGHEST PRIORITY):**
*   **Ensure the `start` and `end` timestamps for each subtitle entry are meticulously accurate.** Both must align perfectly with the *actual beginning and exact conclusion* of the spoken words (including any held notes or extended sounds) or the appearance/disappearance of on-screen text for that specific segment.
*   **Subtitle durations must be short, typically a few seconds.** Long durations (e.g., over 15 seconds) are incorrect and indicate a timing error.
*   **STRICT CHRONOLOGICAL ORDER (CRITICAL):**
*   **Every subtitle entry MUST be in strict chronological order.** The `start` time of any subtitle entry MUST be greater than or equal to the `end` time of the immediately preceding subtitle entry.
*   **Crucially, subtitle segments MUST NOT overlap.** The `start` time of a new segment must be greater than or equal to the `end` time of the previous segment.
*   **Any deviation from strict chronological order or overlapping segments will result in immediate rejection and re-processing of the entire segment.** This is a non-negotiable requirement.
*   Timestamps must always be in `MM:SS` (minutes:seconds).
2.  **COMPREHENSIVE CONTEXTUAL UNDERSTANDING:**
*   **Watch the entire video thoroughly** to understand the visual context, speaker actions, and overall narrative. This holistic understanding is crucial for accurate transcriptions and translations.
*   **Always combine logical sentences or phrases split across multiple subtitle entries** to understand the full, complete meaning before translating. Ensure each translated entry is a coherent part of the overarching sentence.
*   For songs or singing sections, prioritize on-screen lyrics in the video for subtitles over transcribing the singing.
*   If audio is noisy or unclear, leverage *all* contextual cues (visuals, surrounding dialogue, speaker intent, tone) to infer the most probable dialogue.
*   **DO NOT HALLUCINATE:** Only transcribe and translate content that is actually present in the video (spoken or on-screen). Do not invent dialogue or text.
*   **Include relevant on-screen text:** If there is text displayed on screen that is relevant to the video's content, transcribe and translate it as well, ensuring its timing aligns with its appearance on screen.
*   **Example of Holistic Translation:**
*   Original Japanese: "なんでも打ち明けられるママにも" (Subtitle 1) + "言えないことも全部" (Subtitle 2)
*   Incorrect Translation (isolated): "You're like a mom I can confide anything in." + "Even things I can't say to anyone else."
*   Correct Translation (holistic): "I can confide everything," (Subtitle 1) + "everything I can't even tell my mum." (Subtitle 2)
3.  **TRANSLATION ACCURACY & NUANCE:**
*   **Prioritize natural-sounding translations:** Translations should read as if originally written in the target language, avoiding overly literal or awkward phrasing.
*   **Maintain cultural appropriateness:** Adapt idioms, cultural references, and nuances to resonate with the target audience while preserving the original meaning.
*   **Ensure consistency:** Use consistent terminology and phrasing for recurring concepts or names throughout the entire transcription/translation.
4.  **DUAL LANGUAGE PROVISION:**
*   Provide both English and Japanese subtitles for *all* spoken dialogue and relevant on-screen text.
5.  **READABILITY & FORMATTING:**
*   Long sentences MUST be split into multiple, shorter subtitle entries, each with its own start and end time, for better readability on screen. Aim for natural breaks that preserve meaning.
*   Each subtitle entry (English and Japanese) MUST be a maximum of (max_subtitle_chars) characters.
*   Do not use newline characters within a single subtitle entry.
6.  **REVIEW AND REFINE:**
*   Before finalizing, review all generated subtitles to ensure they meet all the above requirements, especially timing precision, chronological order, and translation accuracy.
** Output Format **
* Your entire response must be a single JSON object.
** Example Output **
```json
((
"subtitles": [
"start": "00:00",
"end": "00:04",
"english": "Hello everyone, and welcome to our presentation.",
"japanese": "皆様、プレゼンテーションへようこそ。"
)),
((
"start": "00:05",
"end": "00:06",
"english": "Today, we'll be discussing the future of AI",
"japanese": "本日は、AIの未来について"
)),
((
"start": "00:06",
"end": "00:08",
"english": "and its impact on various industries worldwide.",
"japanese": "その影響について議論します。"
)),
((
"start": "00:09",
"end": "00:11",
"english": "It's a very important topic for all of us.",
"japanese": "これは私たち全員にとって非常に重要なテーマです。"
)),
((
"start": "00:11",
"end": "00:14",
"english": "We sincerely appreciate your attendance today.",
"japanese": "本日はご出席いただき誠にありがとうございます。"
))
]
```
ホロサマパラダイス 開幕
holonatsu Paradise - Opening
hololive production
#ホロサマパラダイス
#holonatsuParadise
ホロ夏パラダイス
holonatsu Paradise
ときのそら, ロボ子さん, AZKi, さくらみこ, 星街すいせい
Tokino Sora, Robocosan, AZKi, Sakura Miko, Hoshimachi Suisei
赤井はあと, 白上フブキ, 夏色まつり, アキ・ローゼンタール
Akai Haato, Shirakami Fubuki, Natsuiro Matsuri, Aki Rosenthal
癒月ちょこ, 百鬼あやめ, 大空スバル
Yuzuki Choco, Nakiri Ayame, Oozora Subaru
白上フブキ, 戌神ころね, 猫又おかゆ, 大神ミオ
Shirakami Fubuki, Inugami Korone, Nekomata Okayu, Ookami Mio
白銀ノエル, 宝鐘マリン, 兎田ぺこら, 不知火フレア
Shirogane Noel, Houshou Marine, Usada Pekora, Shiranui Flare
姫森ルーナ, 角巻わため, 常闇トワ, 天音かなた
Himemori Luna, Tsunomaki Watame, Tokoyami Towa, Amane Kanata
雪花ラミィ, 尾丸ポルカ, 桃鈴ねね, 獅白ぼたん
Yukihana Lamy, Omaru Polka, Momosuzu Nene, Shishiro Botan
鷹嶺ルイ, ラプラス・ダークネス, 博衣こより, 風真いろは
Takane Lui, La+ Darknesss, Hakui Koyori, Kazama Iroha
アユンダ・リス, ムーナ・ホシノヴァ, アイラニ・イオフィフティーン
Ayunda Risu, Moona Hoshinova, Airani Iofifteen
クレイジー・オリー, アーニャ・メルフィッサ, パヴォリア・レイネ
Kureiji Ollie, Anya Melfissa, Pavolia Reine
カエラ・コヴァルスキア, こぼ・かなえる, ベスティア・ゼータ
Kaela Kovalskia, Kobo Kanaeru, Vestia Zeta
森カリオペ, 一伊那尓栖, 小鳥遊キアラ
Mori Calliope, Ninomae Ina'nis, Takanashi Kiara
オーロ・クロニー, IRyS, ハコス・ベールズ
Ouro Kronii, IRyS, Hakos Baelz
ネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト, シオリ・ノヴェラ, フワワ・アビスガード, モココ・アビスガード, 古石ビジュー
Nerissa Ravencroft, Shiori Novella, FUWAWA Abyssgard, MOCOCO Abyssgard, Koseki Bijou
ラオーラ・パンテーラ, エリザベス・ローズ・ブラッドフレイム, セシリア・イマーグリーン, ジジ・ムリン
Raora Panthera, Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame, Cecilia Immergreen, Gigi Murin
火威青, 一条莉々華, 音乃瀬奏, 轟はじめ, 儒烏風亭らでん
Hiodoshi Ao, Ichijou Ririka, Otonose Kanade, Todoroki Hajime, Juufuutei Raden
輪堂千速, 水宮枢, 響鳴リおな, 崎々々ヴぃヴィ, 虎金妃笑
Rindo Chihaya, Mizumiya Saki, Hiodoshi Riona, Isaki Rui, Koganetsuki Egao
ホロ夏パラダイス
holonatsu Paradise
2025.7.9 (Wed.) 20:00~
hololive RESORT
ホロライブの夏がきた！
Hololive's summer is here!
ホロ夏パラダイス！
Holonatsu Paradise!
イェーイ！
Yay!
さあ、今年も夏の季節がやってきた！
So, summer has arrived again this year!
ホロ夏ってことで水着でお届けしてるんですけど。はい、水着です、水着、水着、水着。
Since it's holonatsu, we're in swimsuits. Yes, swimsuits, swimsuits, swimsuits!
おや、水着じゃない子がいる。
Oh? There's someone who's not in a swimsuit.
ああー！
Aaaah!
まあ、ね、今日からね、ホロ夏どんどん暑くなっていくんだけど…
Well, from today, holonatsu will keep getting hotter, but...
水着じゃない！
Not in a swimsuit!
水着じゃないよ！
You're not in a swimsuit!
ふわもこも脱ごうよ！
FUWAMOCO, take yours off too!
脱げ！
Take it off!
その服水着じゃない！
Those clothes aren't a swimsuit!
ずるい！
So unfair!
欲しいもんね！
We want one!
水着欲しい！
We want a swimsuit!
ねえ！
Yeah!
涼しいよ！
It's so cool!
欲しいなあ…
We want one...
脱がすって何？
What do you mean, 'undress'?
うらやましい！
We're so jealous!
可愛い水着！
Such a cute swimsuit!
キツいでしょう？
It must be tight, right?
何？脱がす？
What? Undress?
キツくない！セクシーじゃない！セクシーじゃない！
It's not tight! It's not sexy! Not sexy!
可愛い水着！
A cute swimsuit!
ずるい！
So unfair!
もらえるといいね。
Hope you can get one.
はい。というわけでね、ではそろそろ改めて自己紹介からいきましょう。
Alright then, let's start over with introductions.
じゃあ、まずFUWAMOCO！
Okay, first up, FUWAMOCO!
はい！チワワじゃないよ！フワワだよ！
Okay! I'm not a chihuahua! I'm FUWAWA!
チワワじゃないよ！モココだよ！
I'm not a chihuahua! I'm MOCOCO!
ホロライブEnglish -Advent-の魔界の番犬シスターズ！二人合わせて、FUWAMOCOです！
The demonic guard dog sisters from hololive English -Advent-! Together, we're FUWAMOCO!
バウバウ！
BAU BAU!
（歓声）
(Cheering)
可愛い！では、次はラプラス！
Okay, next up is La+!
イエスマイダーク！
Yes, my dark!
ひれ伏せよ！
Bow before me!
我が輩のお名前は…あ、すいません。我が輩のお名前は、ラプラス・ダークネスだ！
My name... Oh, sorry. My name is La+ Darknesss!
可愛い！
Cute!
一人だけ…
She's the only one...
次、いいのね？よし
Alright then, next up!
じゃあ、ゾン、ババーン！
All right, Zom-baboom!
みんなのかわいいゾンビアイドル
Your friendly neighborhood zombie idol,
くくくくくクレイジー・オリーです！
Ku-ku-ku-ku-Kureiji Ollie desu!
ホロライブIDの新しい時代へ！
Love-love-love-love! The new generation of idols has arrived!
あい、ばうばう！
I... Bau bau!
待って！
Wait, that's not it...
えっと、あと一人残って
There's one person left...
マリンじゃないよ、ノエルだよ！
Not Marine, but Noel!
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルです。
I'm hololive 3rd Gen's Shirogane Noel.
よろしくお願いします。
It's a pleasure to be here!
はい！
Alright!
ノエルじゃないよ！マリンだよ！
Not Noel, but Marine!
団長じゃないよ！ばうばう！
Not Danchou... Bau bau!
やめてやめて！
Stop it, stop it!
怖い怖い怖い！
Scary, scary!
Scary, scary, scary!
家庭内暴力だ！
This is domestic abuse!
船長！
The captain is...
仲良しだ！
They're getting along.
はい、てことで、ホロ夏パラダイスの最初の
Alright, so, Holonatsu Paradise's first...
お仕事を、開幕式を、この6人でやっていきたいと思います！
big job, the opening ceremony, will be hosted by the six of us!
イェーイ！
Yay!
まず、ホロ夏パラダイスについて、ちょっとご紹介をします。
First, I'll briefly introduce Holonatsu Paradise.
ホロ夏パラダイスは、ホロライブならではの夏を全力でお届けする熱いイベントとなっております！
Holonatsu Paradise is an exciting event delivering a uniquely hololive summer!
hololive RESORT
期間中、大型VRChat企画や、特別な配信、
During the event, there'll be a big VRChat project, special streams,
夏を盛り上げる新曲公開などがあり、とにかく激アツ！
and a new song release! It's going to be super exciting!
見どころ盛りだくさんでやっていきますよー！
We're going all out, so look forward to it!
さっきのオープニングの動画でさ、
In the opening video...
みんな、新しい衣装を着てたけど、あれもホロ夏のやつ？
everyone was wearing new outfits. Are those for Holonatsu?
そうなんですよー！
Yes, that's right!
7日に公開されたホロ夏パラダイスのティザー動画で初披露となったオリジナル夏衣装！
The teaser video for Holonatsu Paradise, released on the 7th, featured the debut of our original summer outfits!
じゃん！こちらです！
Here they are!
かわいい！
So cute!
そう、みんなの個性に合ったデザインになっております。
The designs are tailored to each of our personalities!
めっちゃ様！
It's amazing!
グッズになる！
This is merchandise-worthy!
間違いない！
For sure!
グッズはね、どうなんでしょうねって感じですが。
Well, as for merchandise... we'll have to see about that!
こちらの夏衣装のイラストは、ホロライブ公式Xやホロ夏特設ページにて、配信後の21時より公開予定なんで
The illustrations for these summer outfits will be posted on the official hololive X and Holonatsu special page at 9 PM after the stream.
ぜひご覧ください。
Please check them out!
はい、今日はね、ホロ夏パラダイスに関するお知らせがたくさんあるんですよ！
Yes, we have a lot of announcements about Holonatsu Paradise today!
でも、ただ発表するだけじゃ面白くない。
But it's no fun just announcing them.
なに？
What?!
というわけで、ここからは、マリンチームとノエルチームに分かれて
So, from now on, we'll split into Team Marine and Team Noel
ゲームで対決し、勝った方がお知らせできるってのはどうだい？
and compete in a game! The winning team gets to make the announcement!
面白いね！
That sounds fun!
勝ったチームには、お知らせしたご褒美として、素敵なプレゼントもあるよ！
And as a reward for the winning team, there's a fantastic present!
やったー！
Yay!
イェーイ！
やる気出てきたなー！
I'm getting pumped!
やっていきましょう！
Let's do this!
じゃあ早速チーム分けを、発表したいと思います。
Alright, I'd like to announce the teams right away.
こちら！
Here they are!
はい！
Yes!
ﾃｹﾃｹﾃｹﾃｹ…
Chugga-chugga-chugga...
うおー！
Whoa!
はい、こちらですわ。頭にね、ハイビスカス付いたと思う。これで色分けされているので。
Yes, here we are. You have hibiscus on your heads.
They're color-coded.
じゃあ、ちょっとチームで分かれましょうか。
Okay, let's split into our teams.
あっち行けお前！
Go over there, you.
こっちだよ。
This way.
分かれろ。
Move it.
おいで、もこちゃん。
Come on, Moco-chan.
ママにもぶたれたことないのに。
I've never even been hit by my mom!
はいって感じで。どうですか、このチーム。
And that's that. How's this team?
いけるか？ やれるやれる！ いいじゃん！
Can we do it? We can! We can! Looks good!
色がね、いい感じ。
The colors look good.
おお？
Oh-ho?
こっちもいい感じだけどね。
This team looks good too.
いいじゃん。
It's good!
いける、いける！
We can do this.
いい感じ、いい感じ。
Looks good, looks good.
セクシーポーズ！
Sexy pose!
おしり振って。
Shake your butt!
いくぞー！
Let's go!
おしりふってー！
Shake that booty!
じゃあ早速、最初の対決に行きましょう！
Alright, let's get to our first showdown!
hololive RESORT
最初の対決は、これだ！
The first showdown is... this!
夏が来たなら
If summer has come,
ヤシの木をぶっ倒せ！
knock down the palm trees!
サマーパームシュート！
Summer Palm Shoot!
サマーパームシュート
Summer Palm Shoot
え、ルールはこちらです。
The rules are here.
はい。
Yes.
ルール説明
サマーパームシュート
Rule Explanation
Summer Palm Shoot
プールに浮かぶヤシの木6本。
このヤシの木に向かって、ヤシの実を蹴って倒します。
There are six palm trees in the pool.
Kick coconuts at them to knock 'em down.
サッカー！
Soccer!
サッカー。
Soccer.
え、制限時間は2分。2分以内に全てを倒すか、より多く倒した本数で競う対決となっております。
The time limit is two minutes.
It's a showdown to either knock down all of them
or knock down the most in two minutes.
当てるのが難しい小さなヤシの木や、動くヤシの木もあるので頑張ってください！
There are small, hard-to-hit palm trees
and moving ones, so do your best!
はい！
Okay!
こちらのゲームはチームごとに1回ずつ挑戦していきます。
Each team gets one try at this game.
Okay!
まぁ、こっちはね。まぁ見ての通り、もうめっちゃ強そうだから。
Well, as you can see, our team looks super strong.
うそつけ。
You wish.
あっ、ちょ、おい！
What was that?
でもうちらのチームもね、ほら。
But our team too, look!
よいぞ、強いぞ。
Alright! I'm strong!
ちょっと強いぞ！
I'm a little strong!
ノエルさんちょっと怪しい。
Noel, you're a bit suspicious.
でもさ、ラプちゃんがね、ラプちゃんボールの友達だよね？
But Lapu-chan, you're friends with balls, right?
だから…サッカーやってる。
So... you play soccer, right?
サッカーやってそう。
You look like you play soccer.
サッカー少年だこいつは。大丈夫だよ。
She's a soccer boy. It's fine.
さあ、じゃあサッカーやろうぜ。
Alright, let's play soccer then.
やろうぜ！なんとかなるさ。
Let's do it. We'll manage somehow.
でもでも、最初の挑戦どっちからやりますか？
But, but, who wants to take the first challenge?
じゃんけんで決めよう。
Let's decide with rock-paper-scissors.
じゃあ、じゃんけん...ふん！
Okay, rock-paper-scissors... hmph!
一応ホロダンスじゃんけんの...うちは...
For the Holo Dance Janken... I am...
うちには勝者です！
...the winner!
最強のお主の記録を破る。
I'll break your ultimate record.
お主のじゃんけんキングの記録をマリンがブチブチにぶち破ってやる！
I, Marine, will shatter your Janken King record!
行くぞ。
Let's go.
オッケー。それじゃあ行くぞ。
Okay. Alright, let's go.
はい！
Okay!
最初はグー、じゃんけん...
Rock, paper, scissors...
おっとっとっと
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
（混沌とした叫び声とじゃんけん）
(chaotic screaming and rock-paper-scissors)
勝った！やった！
I won! Yay!
（さらにカオス）
(more chaos)
さあ、どっちが先にやりますか？先攻後攻。
Alright, who's going first? First or second?
どっちがいい？
Which do you prefer?
まあ、どっちでもいいんですけど皆は。
Well, I don't mind either way, everyone.
じゃあ、最初やっちゃう？
So, shall we go first?
オッケー！
Okay!
うん、オッケー！
Yeah, okay!
ということで、最初にいかしていただきましょうか。
So, let's have you go first.
では準備をしてくださいよ。
Please get ready then.
戦意喪失させてやるぜ。
I'll make you lose your will to fight.
かかってこいよマジで。
Bring it on, seriously.
ちなみにあのチームの意気込みとか聞いて。
By the way, ask them about their team's spirit.
聞いてやるよじゃあ、意気込みどうぞ。
Okay, I'll ask. Go ahead with your aspirations.
えー、やっぱり…。
Umm, as expected...
言っちゃって言っちゃって。
Go on, say it.
じゃあ戦意喪失させる。戦意喪失させてやる。
Okay, we'll make them lose their will to fight.
もう全部倒してね、このゲームあれじゃん、消化試合じゃんみたいに。
We'll knock 'em all down and this'll just be a formality.
いくぞー！
Let's go!
準備するか。
Let's get ready.
そしたらこっちだって。
Well then, on our side...
その時間を超える速度で倒すんだが。
we'll defeat you at a speed that surpasses time.
そうだそうだ！
Yeah, that's right!
マジでこうやっていきってるやつは本当に弱いんだからな。
People who brag like this are always really weak.
たぶんあっちのほうが弱いんだろうな。
They're probably the weak ones.
一斉に蹴っちゃダメだから。誰が蹴るとか決めたか？
You can't kick all at once. Have you decided who's kicking?
なんとなくのノリで良い感じ。
We'll just go with the flow, it's fine.
やってるやろいつも。
You always do it, right?
サッカー部だから。
Because we're the soccer club.
はい！じゃあ、どうですか？準備はよろしいですか？
Okay! So, how is it? Are you ready?
いいぞ、いいよ！
Alright, it's good!
はい、それではいきましょう！
Okay, let's go!
じゃあ、サマーパームシュート、レッツサマー！
Okay, Summer Palm Shoot, Let's Summer!
スタート！
Start!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
頑張れ！大丈夫大丈夫。
Go for it! It's fine, it's fine.
第一小学生の…
The first elementary schooler's...
あ、こより、危ないよ危ない。
Ah, Koyori, careful, careful.
あれはあれでの戦意が…
That itself is a will to fight...
（悲鳴）
(screaming)
うまい！
Nice!
何やってんの！
What are you doing!
ラプ様！
Laplus-sama!
破壊しないでください。
Please don't destroy it.
小学生の…
The elementary schooler's...
足りない！
Not enough!
動いたんだけどね。
It moved, though.
ラプラスのが難しいね。
Laplus's is difficult.
ほらほら！行け！
Come on, come on! Go!
ノエル下手くそすぎる。
Noel, you're too bad at this.
ああー！やばい！
Aah! This is bad!
当たらないか！待って！
Can't hit it! Wait!
力が、力が欲しい！
I need strength, strength!
よし、大丈夫か？これ難しいよ！
Alright, are you okay? This is hard!
奥の難しいね。
The one in the back is hard.
おおー！うまい！
Ooh! Nice!
すごい！めっちゃ飛んでる！
Amazing! It's flying so far!
頑張れー！
Go for it!
やった！
Yay!
ついに！
Finally!
いけるいけるいける！
You can do it, do it, do it!
やばいよ、4本倒れてる！
This is crazy, 4 are down!
うまいな、むずい！
So good, but it's hard!
おー、うまいじゃん！
Oh, nice!
これ以上倒されたらまずいって。
If any more fall, it's bad.
小さい！惜しい！
It's small! So close!
待って待って！あっち側に行こう！
Wait, wait! Let's go for that one!
10、9、8、7！
10, 9, 8, 7!
決めろ！
Do it!
終了！
Finished!
It's over!
これは隠し玉はふわわじゃん。
This secret weapon is Fuwawa.
めっちゃ倒してくれたね。
She knocked down a lot, didn't she?
やった！
Yay!
これまずいね。すごいすごい。
This isn't good. She's amazing.
でもみんな倒したよね。やった！
But everyone knocked one down, right? Yay!
やったー！やったみんなで！
Yay! We all did it!
チーム組む？チーム組む？
Let's team up? Let's team up?
チーム！
Team!
じゃあ結果はですね
Okay, so the results are...
5本かな？おーすごい！
Maybe 5? Oh, amazing!
すごーい！もっと行きたかったな。
Amazing! I wanted to get more.
結果受けてどうですか？
How do you feel about the results?
いやもう余裕だよね、これ。
Well, this was a piece of cake, right?
お前そんなに活躍してないだろう。
You didn't do that much.
いや、1本倒したからね。
Hey, I knocked one down, you know.
みんなの力だからね。
It's thanks to everyone's power.
やったー！
Yay! We did it!
じゃあもう交代しますよ。調子乗らないでね。
Okay, we're switching now. Don't get cocky.
恥ずかしくね？
Isn't that embarrassing?
バトンもらいました。
I've received the baton.
次！
Next!
こっちにはね、ふわわと同じ血を受け継いだもこちゃんがいるんだから。
On this side, we have Mococo, who inherited the same blood as Fuwawa.
もこちゃんが決めるから！
Mococo will decide it!
一応そうです。
Supposedly, yes.
正直ふわわのことどう思う？
Honestly, what do you think of Fuwawa?
もこちゃんたぶん全然何も倒してない。
Mococo probably didn't knock down anything at all.
倒してない。
I didn't.
見せつけてくれ。
Show us what you've got.
頑張るからね。
I'll do my best.
いいですか？ざここじゃないよ。
Okay? Not 'zako-ko'.
準備準備、はい準備します。
Get ready, get ready. Okay, getting ready.
順番はじゃあマリン、もこ、
Okay, the order will be Marine, Moco...
ちゃん、Ollieでいきますか？
Ollie, shall we go?
はい。それでは並べましょう。
Yes. Let's line up.
MMO、横並びでね。
M.M.O. Side-by-side.
じゃあ、準備完了です。
Okay, we're all ready.
完了ですか？はい。
Ready? Yes.
準備はいいということで、
Since you're ready,
では、いきましょう！
let's go!
はい。うん。
Yes. Okay.
せーの
Ready, set...
せーのいる？
Do we need a "Ready, set"?
いいから、いいから、笑わないで。
It's fine, it's fine. Don't laugh.
じゃ、せーの
Okay, ready, set...
シャワーポーズシュート！
Shower Pose Shoot!
レッツサマー！
Let's Summer!
イェーイ！
Yay!
スタート！
Start!
はい！
Yes!
わー！すごい！
Whoa! Amazing!
力強く投げてる！
Such powerful throws!
うわああ！
Waaaaah!
次は！
Next!
ナイス！
Nice!
当たった！
It hit!
やったぜ！
Yeah!
なんか力強い！
So strong!
いいね、いいね！
Nice, nice!
倒れないぞ！
It's not falling!
みんな倒れないね。
They're not falling.
マリンさん、後半疲れるよ。
Marine, you'll get tired in the second half.
むずい、むずい、むずい！
It's hard, hard, hard!
そうだよね！
Right!
大丈夫、大丈夫。
It's okay, it's okay.
うわあああ！
Waaaaah!
よっしゃー！
Alright!
すごいすごいすごい！
Amazing, amazing, amazing!
惜しかった！
So close!
おりゃ、ナイス！
Oryaa, nice!
2本倒した！
Knocked down two!
見てるからね。
I'm watching, you know.
ほら！
See!
おい、何やってんだ。
Hey, what are you doing?
わー！
Whoa!
うわっ！いける！
Whoa! You can do it!
ラスト1つ！
Last one!
あと1つ！
One more!
大丈夫、大丈夫。
It's okay, it's okay.
1つは欲しいかも。
I kinda want just one.
最後！
Last one!
よかった！
Yes!
よしよしよしよし。
Alright, alright...
むずいんじゃない？
Isn't it hard?
あれうざい。
That one's annoying.
当てて逆に倒れないとかある？
Can you hit it and it *doesn't* fall?
そういうことあるよ。
That happens sometimes.
すり抜けて行ってる。
It's passing right through.
あー！
Aah!
あと1本だよ！
Just one more!
向きが、
The direction is...
巡ってる。
going around.
待って待って、乗らない。
Wait, wait, it's not on.
あ、でも向きが、向きが、今逆向いてる！
Ah, but the direction... it's facing the wrong way!
あと1本よ！1本近くに。
Just one more! There's one nearby.
惜しい！
So close!
マリン！マリン！
Marine! Marine!
後半使う。
Save it for the second half.
疲れてねえし！
I'm not tired!
倒れないって！
It won't fall!
再現VTR。
Like a reenactment video.
30秒！
30 seconds!
マイナスイオンだ！
It's negative ions!
あー！
Aah!
次が、
The next one is...
あー！
Aah!
待って！
Wait!
大丈夫。
It's okay.
なんだなんだなんだ。
What, what, what.
あと20秒。
20 seconds left.
なんで倒れない？
Why won't it fall?
なんで？なんで？
Why? Why?
15秒。
15 seconds.
めっちゃ耐えてる、あの木！
That tree is really holding on!
おい、何やってる。
Hey, what are you doing?
あと10秒。
10 seconds left.
5本も残ってる！
There are still 5 left!
5本じゃない。
Not five.
4、3、
Four, three...
2、1...
two, one...
終了！
Time's up!
いやー！
Nooooo!
疲れすぎた…
I'm so tired...
お疲れ。
Good work.
ちょっと待って。
Wait a minute.
なんと！
What!
ま、結果は見て…なんですが。
Well, looking at the results... however...
足なめます、ペロペロペロ。
I'll lick your feet, lick lick lick.
まさかの…
No way...
やめろ。
Stop it.
6本全部！
All six of them!
やったー！
We did it!
Ollie！
Ollie!
やったー！
Yay!
強すぎ。
Too strong.
はい、ということで、
So, with that...
すごい。
Amazing.
すごかった。
That was amazing.
マジ強え。
Seriously strong.
すごい。
Amazing.
マジかよ。
Seriously?
やばいっすね。
That's crazy.
おい、見たかうちのオリーちゃん。
Hey, did you see our Ollie?
いや、最後の最後でね。
Yeah, right at the very end.
おい、コバンザメじゃねえか。
Hey, she's like a remora.
オリちゃんめちゃくちゃ疲れてる。
Ollie's really tired.
じゃあ、ちょっと改めまして、あの、いいですか？一言。
Alright, let's start over. Is it okay if I say a word?
あの、では、えー、勝者、え、マリンチーム！
Okay then, uh, the winner is Team Marine!
イェーイ！
Yay!
うわあ！すごいよ！
Whoa! That's amazing!
強かったね！すごい！
We were strong! Amazing!
勝った我々には、なんとご褒美があります。
And for our victory, we get a reward.
えぇ！？
What?!
ご褒美はこちら！
The reward is this!
ココナッツミルク、ココナッツオイル、ナタデココなど
Coconut milk, Coconut oil, Nata de coco, etc.
2キロ相当
2kg worth of coconut-related products!
2キロ？！
2 kilos?!
もっと美しくなっちゃう！
We'll become even more beautiful!
そしてね、何、何をさ、まったり見てるのか知らないけど、
And also, I don't know why you're just standing there,
負けたチームには、罰ゲームしてもらいます！
but the losing team has to do a penalty game!
いやー！
No!
罰ゲーム！
Penalty game!
ショックを受けすぎですよ！
You're too shocked!
何も考えなかった... 罰ゲームって何？
I wasn't thinking about that... What's the penalty?
罰ゲームはこちらです！
The penalty game is this!
ヤシの実を使って１発ギャグ！
A one-shot gag using coconuts!
いやー！
No!
楽しみ、楽しみ！
I'm looking forward to it!
え、これって、ちなみに、え、一人？
Uh, by the way, is it just one person?
えっ、これは代表者一人が
Uh, one representative from the team
やってください。誰がやりますか？
will do it. Who's it going to be?
リーダーだよね。
The leader, right?
リーダー。
The leader.
ラプちゃん、さっき何個倒した？
Lapu-chan, how many did you knock down earlier?
一個。あれ一個か、じゃあ。
One. Oh, just one, then.
でも我輩の方が惜しかったよね。一発で当てたよね。
But I was closer, right? I hit it on the first try.
ほらほら！のえちゃんの最初のクソザコシュートのせいで負けたんだよ。
See? We lost because of Noel-chan's crappy shot at the start.
諦めろ。
Give it up.
ちなみにあのヤシの実は、あれなんですか？2個っていけるの？1個しかない？
By the way, about those coconuts... can I use two? Or is there only one?
2個で、2個いけますか？
Two? Can you use two?
2個、お前、お前なんか察しちゃった？
Two... you, did you figure something out?
察しが良すぎ。
You're too perceptive.
察すな、察すな！
Don't figure it out, don't figure it out!
じゃあ2個に、用意してもらって。
Okay, please prepare two for me.
では、罰ゲームやる人は準備していただいて。
Alright, will the person doing the penalty get ready?
はーい。
Okay.
さあ、いいですかね、準備を。
Alright, are you ready?
やばい、なんか察しちゃったけど。
Oh no, I think I've figured it out.
やめてなんですけど。
Please stop.
じゃあ、準備はよろしいですか？のえちゃん。
Well then, are you ready, Noel-chan?
はい。
Yes.
それでは、のえちゃんの、一発ギャグまで、3、2、1！
And now, for Noel-chan's one-shot gag in 3, 2, 1!
おい！
Hey!
あー、ボインボインボイン。
Ah, boing boing boing.
なんか母性で大きくなっちゃった。赤ちゃんいないかなー、よしよし。
My motherly instincts made them grow. Any babies? There there.
ちゅーちゅー。あ、大きい！
Slurp slurp. Oh, you're big!
ココナッツ味！
It tastes like coconut!
マジで見たくなかったんすけど、先輩！
I really didn't want to see that, Senpai!
これ、オフィシャルチャンネルでいいんですか？
Is this okay for the official channel?
いいでしょう。
It's fine.
ちょ、公式チャンネルかどうかを占ってみた。
I tried to divine if this was the official channel.
なんなのそれ？
What was that?
見てるんすよ。
Everyone's watching.
いいんですか？これで。
Is this really okay?
はい、ご褒美も頂いたのでね。はい、ホロ夏パラダイスのお知らせをしていきましょう！
Since we got our reward... let's move on to the HoloNatsu Paradise announcements!
え、まずは注目コンテンツを紹介します。
First, let's introduce the featured content.
ホロ夏パラダイス期間中は特別な配信や動画が盛りだくさんなんです。
During HoloNatsu Paradise, there will be lots of special streams and videos.
なんと！
No way!
まず1つ目は！ホロなつPiece!
And the first one is HoloNatsu Piece!
え、本日から7月26日土曜日まで参加メンバーの個人チャンネルにて...
Starting today until Saturday, July 26th, on the participating members' individual channels...
夏がテーマのショート動画が毎日投稿されます。
a summer-themed short video will be posted every day.
すごい！
Amazing!
え、みんなどんなショート撮ったの？
Hey, what kind of short did you all film?
どんなの撮ったの？
What kind did you film?
内緒！
It's a secret!
内緒かよ。
It's a secret?!
18日から先は誰が出るかお楽しみです。
Well, we'll have to wait and see who's up after the 18th.
ショート動画ならね、もう気軽に見られると思うので、ぜひ全員コンプリートを目指して、皆さん見てください。
It's a short, so it's easy to watch. So please, try to watch them all!
見てね！見てね！
Watch it!
そして7月25日26日は、大大大大大注目！
And on July 25th and 26th, we have a huge, huge event!
はい、イベント超目白押しです。
The events are really packed!
どんなことをするのかというとこちらです。
What are we doing? You ask? Here it is!
はい、歌枠リレー！
Yes, a song relay!
なんと50人近いホロライブメンバーが7月25日の19時から翌日の17時までほぼ休みなくリレー形式で歌枠を行います。
Nearly 50 hololive members will be in a relay from July 25 at 19:00 until 17:00 the next day, singing with almost no breaks.
イェーイ！
Yeah!
我々も参加していますので、
We're participating too.
ぜひ聴きに来てください。
So please come and listen.
そのあと、7月26日18時からは
After that, on July 26th at 18:00...
こちら、ちょっとノエちゃんにバトンタッチします。
I'll pass the baton to Noel-chan.
その後、7月26日18時から、私、白銀ノエルと、スバちゃんラミィのビッグ3プレゼンツ、ホロライブ尻相撲大会を開催します。
After that, on July 26 at 18:00, Shirogane Noel, Subaru-chan, and Lamy, the Big 3 present... a hololive Butt Sumo Tournament!
なに？！でかい！
What?! That's huge!
夏らしくね、水着でビッグ3を含む7人で、熱い戦いを繰り広げます。最強の尻は一体誰なのか、ぜひご覧ください。
That's right! Just like summer, in swimsuits! Seven members including the Big 3 will have a heated battle. Who has the strongest butt? Be sure to watch!
うーん、最強の尻を決める大会ね。
Ooh... A tournament to decide the strongest butt, huh?
いやー、尻相撲。
Yes, butt sumo!
誰が尻がナンバーワンなんだろう。
Whose butt is number one?
マリンなんだから。
Mine, of course!
マリンは出場しないんですけど。あっ、そうか、しないんだけど。
But you're a host. I won't be competing.
まあ、そんな大会があるんだ。ふん、ちょっと覚えときます。
So there's a tournament like that. Hmm, I'll remember this.
覚えててください。
Yes, please do.
うーん、尻相撲大会か。
Butt sumo tournament...
すごいけど。
So amazing.
ちなみにですね、明日の、え、20時からラミィのチャンネルでこの大会に関する事前配信も行いますのでぜひこちらもご覧ください。お願いします。
By the way, tomorrow at 20:00 on Lamy's channel, there will be a preliminary stream for this tournament, so please check that out too. Please!
はい、えっと、そして26日尻相撲大会、配信後の21時からは、
And on the 26th, after the butt sumo tournament stream, at 21:00...
綺々羅々ヴィヴィ
Kikirara Vivi
響咲リョナ
Isaki Riona
セシリア・イマーグリーン
Cecilia Immergreen
フワワ・アビスガード
Fuwawa Abyssgard
シオリ・ノヴェラ
Shiori Novella
こぼ・かなえる
Kobo Kanaeru
アユンダ・リス
Ayunda Risu
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
アキ・ローゼンタール
Aki Rosenthal
アーニャ・メルフィッサ
Anya Melfissa
白上フブキ
Shirakami Fubuki
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
ビーチで対決！ホロナツクイーン決定戦 in VRChat
Beach Showdown! holonatsu Queen Gauntlet in VRChat
はい、というわけで、ビーチで対決！ホロナツクイーン決定戦 in VRChatの開催をいたします。
So, we'll be holding the "Beach Showdown! holonatsu Queen Gauntlet in VRChat"!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ホロナツ特設VRCゲームワールドを舞台に、優勝者『ホロナツクイーン』を決定するVRchatを使用したホロナツパラダイス最大の祭典です。
This is a tournament battle held in a special holonatsu VRChat game world to decide the winner, the holonatsu Queen, and it's holonatsu Paradise's biggest festival!
VRChatとは、世界中の人とアバターで交流できる、仮想空間のソーシャルプラットフォームです。
VRChat is a social platform in a virtual space where you can interact with people from all over the world through avatars.
そんなVRChatを使ったホロライブ大型企画は、初の試みになります。
This is the first time a major hololive project has used VRChat!
今回、約40名のホロメンが参加します。
About 40 Holo-members will participate this time.
MCは白上フブキ、アーニャ・メルフィッサ、森カリオペの3人。
The MCs are Shirakami Fubuki, Anya Melfissa, and Mori Calliope.
大会の舞台はVRChatの人気ワールドをホロ夏バージョンに特別に改装したものになります。
The stage is a specially modified Holonatsu version of a popular VRChat world.
どんなゲームか少しだけ紹介します。
I'll briefly introduce the games we have.
まずは、ハリセンチャンプ。
First up is Harisen Champ.
ハリセンを持って海へ突き落とし合う1対1のゲームです。
It's a one-on-one game of knocking each other into the sea with a paper fan.
ハリセンで戦うホロメンたちの勇姿をぜひ応援してください。
Please cheer on our brave Holo-members fighting with paper fans.
次に、スイカスマッシュ！
Next, Suika Smash!
とにかくスイカを叩きまくれ！そして勝て！
Just keep smashing the watermelons and win!
スイカの飛距離で勝負が決まる個人戦のゲームになります。
It's a solo game where victory is decided by how far you hit the watermelon.
最後は、ギガス！
And finally, GIGAS!
巨人側と人間側に分かれて戦う迫力のバトルゲーム。
It's an intense battle game pitting giants against humans.
ホロメンが巨大化しちゃう！VRならではの演出もお楽しみに。
The Holo-members can become giants! Enjoy the unique VR experience!
大会本番へ向け、ホロメン向けにいつでも遊べるワールドを開放します。
For the main event, we're opening a world where Holo-members can play anytime.
本番まで練習の様子を配信するのはOKです。
It's okay to stream your practice sessions before the main event.
そして視聴者の皆様も遊びに行けるワールドが登場します。
And now, a world that our viewers can also visit!
本大会でロビーとなるビーチワールドをVRChatにて一般開放。
The beach world lobby for this tournament will be made public on VRChat.
アクセスURLはホロプロ公式Xにて投稿します。
The access URL will be posted on the official HoloPro X account.
ぜひ遊びに入ってハッシュタグホロ夏パラダイスで思い出を投稿してください。
Please come play and post your memories with the hashtag #holonatsuParadise.
リリカとカナデがVRCのゲーム大会で使うメタクエストのコラボ配信も行います。
Ririka and Kanade will also be doing a collaboration stream with Meta Quest.
ホロ夏ステージもプレイするので、こちらもぜひご覧になってください。
They'll be playing on the Holonatsu stage, so please be sure to watch.
ああ、盛りだくさんだなあ。
Ah, so much stuff!
楽しい!
So many things!
すごい、すごい！
Awesome, awesome!
盛りだくさんよ！
It's packed!
まだまだあります。じゃあお知らせを、もこちゃんお願いします。
There's still more! For the next announcement, Mococo-chan, please.
はい！今流れてるホロ夏パラダイスのテーマ楽曲
Yes! The Holonatsu Paradise theme song that's playing right now...
『藍染 summertime!!』がこの後、7月10日0時より、各種音楽配信サービスでリリースされます！
"Aizome Summertime!!" will be released on music streaming services from 12 AM, July 10th!
やったー！
Yay!
歌ってるメンバーはぺこら先輩、わため先輩、ねねち、リス先輩、こぼ先輩、そしてふわもこ！
The singers are Pekora-senpai, Watame-senpai, Nenechi, Risu-senpai, Kobo-senpai, and FUWAMOCO!
イェーイ！
Yay!
わあ！
Wow!
すごい透明感のある、すごい、あの、青って感じがする青春曲なので、ぜひ聞いてください。
It's a very fresh, blue, summery song, so please check it out!
はい！
Yes!
ミュージックビデオは7月26日にプレミア公開予定となっております。
The music video is scheduled to premiere on July 26th.
こちらもぜひお楽しみに。
Please look forward to that as well.
イェーイ！
Yay!
さらに、ReGLOSSの新曲『美灯-夏-シトラス』のミュージックビデオが明日18時公開です！
Furthermore, the MV for ReGLOSS's new song "Mito Summer Citrus" will be released tomorrow at 6 PM!
こちらもチェックしてみてください。
Please check this out as well.
次のお知らせは、Ollie先輩、お願いします！
For the next announcement, Ollie-senpai, please!
はい、はい！
Yes!
えーと、ホロ夏パラダイスグッズボリューム1がこの後21時より、ホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップにて販売開始となります！
Holonatsu Paradise Goods Vol. 1 will go on sale at 9 PM on the Hololive Production Official Shop!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Tシャツやトートバッグ、カードホルダー、キーホルダー、そしてランダムアクリルチャームなどがあります！
There's a T-shirt, tote bag, card holder, key holder, and random acrylic charms!
ホロナツパラダイス グッズ vol.1
holonatsu Paradise Goods vol.1
ランダムアクリルチャームなど
Random acrylic charms...
夏にぴったりのグッズが勢ぞろい！どれも可愛いよね！
A lineup of goods perfect for summer! They're all so cute!
かわいい！はい。
So cute! Yes.
ホロナツ送料半額キャンペーン
Holonatsu Half-Price Shipping Campaign
この後21時からクーポンコードを入力すると国内送料が半額になるキャンペーンもスタートしますので
A campaign for half-price domestic shipping when you enter the coupon code starts after this at 9pm.
気になる方はぜひ販売ページをチェック！
If you're interested, please be sure to check the sales page!
対象外商品が混ざっていると半額にならないので、そこだけご注意ください。
Please be aware that your shipping won't be half-price if your order includes ineligible items.
お願いします！はい、さらにこちらはご覧ください！
Please do! And take a look at this!
ホロナツパラダイスTシャツがホロアースにも登場！
The holonatsu Paradise T-shirts are also coming to holoearth!
ホロアースに2025年7月10日15:00、ホロナツパラダイスTシャツが登場！
holonatsu Paradise T-shirts are coming to holoearth on July 10, 2025 at 3pm!
明日10日15時より、ホロアースでもホロナツグッズのTシャツが発売されます！
The holonatsu goods T-shirts will go on sale at holoearth tomorrow, the 10th, at 3pm!
イエーイ！
Yay!
現実でもホロアースでもホロナツパラダイスグッズを身につけてホロライブの夏を一緒に盛り上げていきましょう！
Wear the holonatsu Paradise goods in real life and in holoearth and get excited for the hololive summer with us!
イエーイ！盛り上がっていきましょう！
Yay! Let's get hyped!
はい！ということでじゃあ次の対決に参りたいと思います。
Okay then! Let's move on to the next showdown!
さあ、少々準備がありますので、配信を見てくれている君たちにはさっきラプラスが頑張って撮ってたVTRをお楽しみいただきたいと思います。
Since we need a moment to prepare, we'd like you all watching the stream to enjoy the VTR that La+ worked so hard on earlier!
頑張りましたよ。
I did my best!
頑張ったね。頑張ったね。
You did great. You did great.
じゃあ、みんな、こちらをご覧ください！
Alright everyone, please take a look at this!
やった！やった！届いた届いた！
Yes! Yes! It arrived! It arrived!
なに？なに？なんでそんな喜んでるの？
What is it? What is it? Why are you so happy?
どうしたの？見てくださいよ、これ！
What happened? Take a look at this!
何？！何これ？！
What is it?! What is it?
クンカクンカ。いい匂いするね。
Sniff sniff. It smells nice, doesn't it?
これは我輩がさっき注文した、ホロライブオリジナルパッケージのからあげクンBOXだ！
This is the Karaage-kun Box with the hololive original packaging I just ordered!
うわー！からあげクンBOX！
Wow! The Karaage-kun Box!
美味しいよね。オリもからあげクン食べたことあるよ！
It's so yummy. Ollie has had Karaage-kun before too!
フブキも好き！好き！
Fubuki likes it too! She loves it!
そんなからあげクン大好きな皆さんに朗報です！
I've got great news for everyone who loves Karaage-kun!
なんと、みんな大好きからあげクンを販売しているローソンさんとホロライブのコラボキャンペーンが、先日7月8日から始まってるんだ！
A collaboration campaign between hololive and Lawson, who sells everyone's favorite Karaage-kun, just started on July 8th!
コラボキャンペーン！
A collaboration campaign!
我輩も注文したからあげクンBOXホロライブオリジナルパッケージは
The Karaage-kun Box with the hololive original packaging I ordered...
Uber Eats、Wolt、menu、Yahoo!クイックマートの各種デリバリーサービスで数量限定で販売中！
...is available in limited quantities on various delivery services like Uber Eats, Wolt, menu, and Yahoo! QuickMart!
超可愛いローソン限定デザイン！みんなもゲットしてくれよな！
It's a super cute Lawson exclusive design! Make sure you get one!
そしてそして！うおお！我輩がからあげクンに！
And and! Whoa! I've become Karaage-kun!
になっちゃったー！怖い！
I've become one! Scary!
オリジナルボックスにもデザインされていた、吾輩たちのからあげクンなりきりイラストが
The illustration of us dressed as Karaage-kun
オリジナルグッズとなって登場！
is now official merchandise!
わーい！
Hooray!
ホロライブオリジナル装飾が施されたコラボ店舗、
At the collaboration stores with hololive decorations,
ローソン渋谷道玄坂上店と、
the Lawson Shibuya Dogenzakaue branch,
ロッピー、HMVブックスオンラインにて販売中！
Loppi, and HMV & BOOKS online!
こちらもよろしく！
Please check it out!
最後に、お得なお知らせだ！
Finally, some great news!
この配信を見ている方限定で、
For viewers of this stream,
Uber EatsとWoltで使用できるクーポンコードプレゼント！
we're giving away coupon codes for Uber Eats and Wolt!
クーポン！
Coupons!
クーポンコードはホロローソン。
The coupon code is "HoloLawson."
カタカナでホロローソンです！
"HoloLawson" in katakana!
クーポンの期限がそれぞれのサービスで異なるので、お気をつけください！
The expiration dates differ for each service, so please be careful!
最大40%オフのチャンス！
A chance for up to 40% off!
この機会を見逃すな！
Don't miss this opportunity!
うん！
Yeah!
よし、お知らせも終わったし、吾輩はからあげクンを食べようかな。
Alright, the announcements are over, so I think I'll eat some Karaage-kun.
えい、それ！
Here, take this!
いつの間にか持ってないじゃん！
I'm not holding it anymore!
吾輩のからあげクンボックスはどこー！
Where's my Karaage-kun box?!
どろぼう！
Thief!
ラプラス先輩！
Laplus-senpai!
一人占めは良くないですよ！
It's not good to have it all to yourself!
そう！おいしいものは
That's right! Delicious things
みんなで食べよう！そう！
should be shared with everyone! Right!
というわけで、こいつは頂いていくぜ！
So, I'll be taking this!
おい！吾輩のからあげクンボックス！
Hey! My Karaage-kun box!
こらー！
Hey!
詳細は特設サイトを要チェック!!
Check the special website for details!!
※URLは概要欄をご参照ください
※Please refer to the description for the URL
（もぐもぐ）
(Munching sounds)
うまい！
Delicious!
やっぱりチーズ味が最高。
The cheese flavor is the best.
うーん！
Mmm!
辛いのがいいよ...
Spicy is good...
塩味がベストなんよなー
The salt flavor is the best.
うーん...ああ、幸せ。
Mmm... Ahh, I'm so happy.
ついでに夏にぴったりの甘いものとかあったら最高なのに〜な〜
It would be perfect if there were some sweets perfect for summer, too.
確かに〜
True...
それな！
Right?!
ああ！見てあれ！
Ah! Look at that!
え？え？何？
Huh? What? What is it?
あ？
Huh?
あれだよ！
It's that!
え？
Huh?
スイカ？
Watermelon?
わー！スイカだ！
Wow! It's watermelon!
うそ！
No way!
わ、スイカだ！でもなんであんなところに...
Wow, watermelon! But why is it over there?
はぁ、仕方ない。これは取りに行くしかないわね。
Hah, can't be helped. We have to go get it.
ノエル？
Noel?
どっちが早くスイカを持ってこれるか勝負だ！
Let's race to see who can bring back a watermelon first!
望むところです！
I accept your challenge!
初挑戦は、俺ら！
The first challengers are us!
はい！フルーツデリバリー対決！
Yes! Fruit Delivery Battle!
イェーイ！
Yay!
なんだなんだ。
What's this?
はい、すいません。一瞬飛んでましたけど。
Sorry, I zoned out for a sec.
ということで、ルールはこちら！
Anyway, here are the rules!
ルール説明
Rule Explanation
舞台は、全長約20メートルのプールコース
The stage is a 20-meter long pool course.
浮島を飛び渡り、
Jump across the floating islands,
直径10センチ・長さ約4メートルの丸太の上を
and balance across a 10cm diameter, 4m long log
バランスよく進みスイカのもとへ
to reach the watermelons.
トレイを“片手だけで”持ち
Hold the tray with "only one hand".
先に“3つのスイカ”を運んだチームの勝利！
The first team to carry "3 watermelons" wins!
万が一スイカを落としたりプールに落ちたりしても、その場から再開してOK！
If you drop a watermelon or fall, you can restart from that spot. OK!
ルール説明
Rule Explanation
目指せ 夏の最速フルーツ配達王！
Aim to be the fastest fruit delivery king of summer!
浮島を飛び渡り、
Jump across the floating islands,
バランスよく進みスイカのもとへ
and balance your way to the watermelons
直径10cm・長さ約4mの丸太の上を
on a log 10cm wide and 4m long.
トレイを“片手だけで”持ち
Hold the tray with "only one hand."
先に“３つのスイカ”を運んだチームの勝利！
The team that carries "3 watermelons" first wins!
うちらが勝ったわけだけど
We won the last one,
これでも負けたらもうしょうもないけど
but if you lose this, you'll be pathetic.
大丈夫そう？作戦立ててる？
Are you okay? Do you have a strategy?
負けない！
We won't lose!
ラプラスちゃん、どうしたの？
Laplus, what's wrong?
おい、クソガキ元気ないぞ。
Hey, brat, you're not looking so hot.
あれ？苦手なの？
Huh? Are you bad at this?
その角でバランス取れ
Use those horns for balance!
重りだ！ そんなんじゃ均衡取れねえよ！
They're weights! You can't balance with that!
取れねえか。頭重そうだもんな。
You can't? Your head does look heavy.
じゃあ、なんか順番とかどうする？挑戦順。
So, how about the order? Who's going first?
順番は...
The order is...
やっぱ団長がね、ささっと行って活気づけたいのと
Right. As the leader, I'll go first and hype us up.
かっこいい！ 最後はちょっと怖い
So cool! Going last is a bit scary.
最後がいい。 じゃあ最後で。
I wanna go last. Then you can go last.
どうした？元気ねえぞ、おい。
What's wrong? You're not very energetic.
調子狂うやないかい！
You're throwing me off!
生意気にしろ！ うるせえ！
Be more cheeky! Shut up!
無理なんだ。
I can't do it...
大丈夫。大丈夫、かわいい。
It's okay. It's okay, you're cute.
はい、一緒なんや。お母さんいるからね。
Yes, we're a team. Mom's here for you.
お母さん…私も独りになりたいな。
Mom... I want to be on my own.
ママ、ママがいるよ、ほら。
Mom, mom is here, look.
子供じゃないもん！
I'm not a kid!
Mocoちゃん、ほらおいで。何の茶番？
Moco-chan, come here. What is this skit?
優しいけど...
You're kind, but...
うちでやんないとあんた。 そうだよ。
We have to do this ourselves. That's right.
そうです。こっちの順番はリーダーのMarineが行き
Right. For our order, leader Marine will go...
そして、Fuwa?
And then, Fuwawa?
二番？バトルするの？
Second? Are we gonna battle?
バトル？ バトルね。 バトル？
A battle? A battle, right. A battle?
FuwaMoco is winning! Fuwawa winning!
負けたらお前、罰ゲームだからな。
If you lose, it's a penalty game for you.
いやだ！
No way!
はい、って感じで、じゃあ準備はできましたかね。
Okay, so with that, are we ready?
うん、そうだね。 準備よろしいですか？
Yeah, I think so. Are you ready?
さあ、それでは行きましょうか。
Well then, shall we go?
行くよ！せーの！
Let's go! Ready, set!
フルーツデリバリー
Fruits Delivery...
レッツサマー！
Let's Summer!
カンカンって鳴ったら行くよ。
We go when the bell rings.
（カウントダウンとホーンの音）
*Countdown beeps and horn*
行け！頑張れ！
Go! Go for it!
（歓声）
*Cheers*
ノエルちゃん、何してんの！
Noel-chan, what are you doing?!
ボール間違えた！ボール間違えた！
Wrong watermelon! Wrong watermelon!
何で間違えた？ 急いで！
Why did you grab the wrong one? Hurry!
（歓声）
*Cheers*
ノエルさん、いいよ！ 安定！
You got this, Noel-san! Steady!
（叫び声と水しぶき）
*Shouting and splash*
うまい！ うわー！
No way! Awesome!
行け！行け！行け！
Go! Go! Go!
（歓声と叫び声）
*Cheers and shouts*
行け！ うわ！
Go! Whoa!
頑張れ！頑張れ！
Go! Do your best! Do your best!
頑張れ、モコちゃん！ 行け！いける！
Go for it, Moco-chan! Go! You can do it!
（水しぶきと歓声）
*Splash and cheers*
急いで！ 行け！
Hurry! Go!
こよちゃん頑張って！
Go for it, Koyo-chan!
可愛いよ！
You're so cute!
もこもこスイカ！
Mococo, watermelon!
頑張って、マジで。
Seriously, go for it.
大丈夫！ゆっくり！
It's alright! Slowly.
ナイス！やった！
Nice! You did it!
ぱんぱかぱーん！
Pan-pa-ka-paan!
スイカはクリア！
The watermelon is clear!
ゆっくり、ゆっくり！急げ！
Slowly, slowly! Hurry!
おい、プレッシャーかけんなおい！
Hey, don't put pressure on her!
いいぞこよ！
Go Koyo!
集中、集中！
Focus, focus!
行きますよ！
Here I go!
犬かき！
Doggy paddle!
本則！本則！
Full speed! Full speed!
ついてこい、ついてこい！
Keep up, keep up!
もこっこに負けちゃうよ！
You'll lose to Mokoko!
犬かき！早いから！
Doggy paddle! Because I'm fast!
お姉ちゃん！
Big sis!
胸で！胸で！
With your chest!
胸バフ！
Chest buff!
やったー！ナイス！
Yay! Nice!
早い早い！
Fast, fast!
行け！勝てるぞ！
Go! You can win!
ゴーゴーゴー！
Go, go, go!
暗いよ！
It's dark!
ゴーゴーゴー！
Go, go, go!
近いよ！
She's close!
早すぎる！
She's too fast!
おりおりおり！
Ollie, Ollie, Ollie!
やばい！早く！
This is bad! Hurry!
待って！
Wait!
まじで怖い！やばい！
This is seriously scary! This is bad!
やだ！やばい！
No, no! This is bad!
（悲鳴）
(Screaming)
最後まで、最後まで！
Till the very end!
やったー！
We did it!
ゆっくり、ゆっくり！
Slowly, slowly!
当てちゃった！
She hit it!
やった！やった！
We did it! We did it!
大丈夫！
It's okay!
チームワーク！
Teamwork!
やったー！
Yay!
ぱんぱかぱーん！
Pan-pa-ka-paan!
終了！
It's over!
イェーイ！
Yay!
チームで勝てばいい！
It's fine as long as the team wins!
よかった、支えあって。
I'm glad we supported each other.
どちらもね、あの、いいチームワークでしたね。
Both of you had great teamwork.
結果、勝者は、ドゥルルルル…
And the winner is... *drumroll*...
ノエルチーム！
Team Noel!
イェーイ！
Yay!
なんでお前終わったみたいな顔してんだよ！
Why do you look like it's over?!
やったー！
We did it!
いいか？お前が罰ゲームだからな！
Listen up! You're doing the punishment game!
罰ゲームなんてないよ。
There's no such thing!
まあ、一旦ね。
Well, for now...
まだあるからね、罰ゲームね。
There's still more, the punishment game.
えーと、勝ったノエルチームのご褒美です。
Um, here is the prize for the winning Team Noel.
ご褒美はこちら！
The prize is this!
ごほうび！
Reward!
えー？！
Huh?!
ずるい！
Unfair!
最高級スイカがもらえます！
You get a premium watermelon!
やったー！
Yay!
ずるい、ずるい！
Unfair, unfair!
チームで仲良く食べます。
We'll enjoy it together as a team.
スイカ好きー。
I love watermelon.
お前の頭プスー。
Gonna poke Ollie's head, psshh.
食っちゃった、食っちゃった。
I ate it, I ate it.
嬉しいですけど…
I'm happy, but...
罰ゲーム先輩だよ！
You're the punishment game veteran!
罰ゲームじゃないよ！
This isn't a punishment game!
まだ発表してないっす。
It hasn't been announced yet.
ないんですけど
There isn't, but...
でもなんかすごい察しがいいので
you're all very sharp,
まあちょっと言っちゃうんですが
so I'll just go ahead and say it.
もちろんあります罰ゲーム。
Of course, there is a punishment game.
そうですよね。
I knew it.
やったー！
Yay!
はい、ありますよ。
Yes, there is.
じゃあ負けたマリンチームにはこちらをやってもらえます。
The losing Team Marine will have to do this.
だーん！
Ta-da!
罰ゲーム
Punishment Game
えぇ！？
Huh?!
スイカを使って１発ギャグ
A one-shot gag using a watermelon.
一発ギャグ！？
A one-shot gag?!
オリだオリだ！頭抱えてるぞ！
It's gotta be Ollie! She's holding her head!
ヤれるよねオリ
You can do it, Ollie.
できる
I can do it.
できる。できるよ。
You can. You can do it.
今より困られてますよね
You look even more troubled now.
そこはね
That's where you step up.
でもスイカちゃんいいね。偉いね。
But the watermelon is a nice touch. Good job.
素晴らしい。
Amazing.
重みがある
There's a lot on the line.
はい
Okay.
いいですか？じゃ行きますよ。
You ready? Here we go.
掛け声やるので。
I'll do a countdown.
えっと敗者の、え、
Okay, the loser's, uh...
一発、あ、敗者
one-shot... ah, the loser,
え、マリンチームのオリーちゃんの一発ギャグまで
Team Marine's Ollie's one-shot gag...
え、3、2、1、ドンさん！
in... 3, 2, 1, go!
スイカ、割れてないけど
The watermelon isn't broken,
心が割れてる
but my heart is.
ごめんな、傷つけてごめん。
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry for hurting you.
ごめんよ
I'm sorry!
マリンチーム大丈夫ですか？
Team Marine, are you okay?
ナイス！
Nice!
オリーちゃんの心が
Ollie's heart is...
そんなに傷ついてるなんて思わなかった
I didn't think you were hurting that much.
いやいやいや
Well, well, well.
まあでもしっかりはずしたから
But you totally bombed it, so...
すごい切なすぎる
That's so heartbreaking.
ごめん、ごめんよ。
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
心を割ってしまった
We broke her heart.
食べるスイカは甘い、私みたいに。
The watermelon we'll eat is sweet, just like me.
何言ってんだこいつ
What is she talking about?
コンボだ
It's a combo.
ね、すごい良いものを見れた。
Well, I saw something great.
ということでホロ夏パラダイスのお知らせに行きましょうか。
With that, shall we move on to the holonatsu Paradise announcements?
いきましょう！
Let's go!
はい。え、まずは、え、こちら。
Okay. First up is this.
ホロナツパラダイスボイス
holonatsu Paradise Voice
はい、本日、え、20時より、
Starting today at 8 PM,
え、ホロ夏パラダイスボイスが発売されました。やったー！
the holonatsu Paradise Voice Pack has been released! Yay!
やったー！
Yay!
はい、ホロライブメンバーたちとの、え、夏の1日を
It's a voice pack where you can spend a summer day...
一緒に過ごすような内容となっておりますので、
...with hololive members,
ぜひ聞いてみてください。
so please give it a listen.
購入特典
Purchase Bonus
スマートフォン用タレント単独壁紙
Smartphone Wallpaper (Solo Talent Ver.)
購入したタレントのスマートフォン用壁紙がついてくる！
Get a smartphone wallpaper of the talent you purchased!
ぜひチェックしてみてください。
Please be sure to check it out.
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
ほしい！
I want it!
え、続いてはホロカ
Next up is HoloCa.
お。
Oh.
え、ホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームから、
From the Hololive Official Card Game,
8月のイベントで発売される限定商品の一部を先行公開しちゃいます。
we'll be giving you a sneak peek at some of the limited-edition items
しちゃいます！
that will be sold at August events!
なんだ？
What?
それがこちらのホロナツパラダイスのかき下ろしイラストのスリーブとケースがセットになったホロナツパラダイスバージョンのスタートデッキ！
It's this holonatsu Paradise version Start Deck, which comes with sleeves and a case featuring brand-new art!
いえーい！
Yay!
こちらのスタートデッキには特典としてこちら！
And this start deck comes with this as a bonus!
おぉ！
Wow!
限定特典 エールカード！
Limited Edition Yell Card!
ホロナツパラダイスのメインビジュアルデザインの特製エールカードがついてきますので
It comes with a special Yell Card...
ぜひゲットしてみてくださいね。
...featuring the holonatsu Paradise main visual, so please be sure to get it!
これはほしい！
I really want that!
え、続いてホロライブプロダクションの二次創作ゲームブランド、ホロインディーから
Next, from holo Indie, hololive Production's fan game brand,
3タイトルがゲームをより夏らしくするアップデートを
three titles will be getting updates to make them more summery.
7月15日8時、
They'll be released on July 15th at 8...
ま、20時ですね、20時より実施します！
I mean, 8 PM. They will be implemented at 8 PM!
え、まずはホロライブ お宝マイニング
First up is hololive Treasure Mining.
えぇ！？
What?!
まじで！？
For real?!
船長のゲームだ！
It's Senchou's game!
ホロ夏アップデート専用BGMの追加そして
We're adding a new Holo-Natsu BGM, and...
え、最大サイズのお宝を完成させると
when you complete the largest treasure...
対象のお宝のイラストがホロ夏のイラストになります！
the illustration will become a Holo-Natsu version!
え、マジ？すげー！
Amazing!
え、2つ目に、ミリアットデスからは
Second, from Mili-At-Death...
え、ゲーム内のショップで歌うとカリオペさんが、え、カリオペちゃんが水着に変身、そして
if you sing in the shop, Calli-chan will change into her swimsuit, and...
水着を着用している間だけホロ夏パラダイスオリジナル楽曲が流れます！
while she wears it, a Holonatsu Paradise original song will play!
やったー！うおー！
Yay!
いや、可愛いね。セクシーだ。
So cute! So sexy!
うん。え、3つ目は、え、アイドルショーダウン！
Third, from Idol Showdown...
え、こちらは新モード、ビーチボールモードを実装。
we're adding a new Beach Ball Mode.
誰でも簡単に白熱のバレーが楽しめちゃうかも。
You can easily enjoy an intense game of volleyball!
面白い！
Wow!
え、新モード実装に合わせ、メニュー画面とロビー画面がホロ夏バージョンになります。
The menu and lobby screens will also become Holo-Natsu versions!
いいじゃん。えい！え、アップデートの詳細はホロインディー公式Xをチェック。
For update details, check the official Holo Indie X account.
ホロインディーでも夏を楽しもう！
Let's enjoy summer with Holo Indie too!
おー！
Woohoo!
はい、続いてのお知らせは、ふわわちゃん！
Alright, the next announcement is from Fuwawa-chan!
はーい！
Yay!
pixivさんにて、ホロ夏パラダイスイラスト、ショートストーリーコンテスト開催決定！
The Holonatsu Paradise Illustration & Short Story Contests on pixiv are confirmed!
おおー！
Wow!
イラストコンテストでは、ホロライブメンバーの夏らしい姿やホロカーイラストを大募集。
We're looking for summer-themed art of Hololive members or Holo-card illustrations!
最優秀賞に選ばれた方には20万円が贈呈！
The grand prize winner will receive 200,000 yen!
おー！すごい！
Awesome!
CCG賞では、応募したイラストが実際のホロカーに採用されます！
For the CCG Award, your art will be used as an actual Holo-card!
ええー！
Wow!
すごい！いいね！
Amazing!
ねえ！ショートストーリーコンテストでは、夏らしいショートストーリーを募集！
In the Short Story Contest, we're looking for summer-themed short stories!
ビジュアルイラストを使ったオリジナル高画質カードや豪華商品もご用意してます。
We've prepared original high-quality cards and amazing prizes!
すごい！
Amazing!
楽しそうですね！
This is awesome!
応募者全員にイラスト壁紙がもらえる！
All participants will receive a wallpaper!
可愛い！
Awesome!
詳しくはpixivさんのホームページをチェック！
For details, check the pixiv homepage!
チェック！
Check!
皆様のご参加をお待ちしております！
We look forward to your submissions!
はーい！
Yay!
続いてのお知らせは、ラプラス先輩！
The next announcement is from La+ senpai!
吾輩だー！
It's me!
えーと、8月1日よりホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップ、そしてアニメイトさん、コトブキヤさん、ゲーマーズさんの一部店舗でホロ夏フェアを開催します！
Starting Aug 1st, a Holo-Natsu Fair will be held at our shop, Animate, Kotobukiya, and Gamers!
イェーイ！
Yay!
え、キャンペーン期間中、ホロライブ関連商品を税込2000円ご購入いただくごとに、ホロ夏オリジナル衣装の特製ポストカードを1枚プレゼント！
For every 2,000 yen spent, get a special postcard with an original Holo-Natsu outfit!
やったー！
Yay!
店舗ごとにポストカードのデザインが異なりますので、詳細はホロ夏特設ページからご確認ください。
Designs differ by store, so check the Holo-Natsu page for details!
わー！
Wow!
くださーい！
Great!
いや、思ったより多かったんじゃない？
Wow, there's more than I thought!
いや、盛りだくさん！
So much stuff!
すごい！楽しみだね。いっぱいあるね。楽しみー！
This is so exciting! We're excited!
#ホロサマパラダイス
#holonatsuParadise
こよちゃんもコメントしてくれてた！ありがとう、こより！
Koyo-chan was commenting too! Thank you, Koyori!
実装おめでとうかな？
Congrats on the implementation?
３人でお祝いしたもんか。
The three of us celebrated.
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
すごいですね。
That's amazing.
さあさあ、もう盛りだくさんでしたが、いよいよホロサマが始まっていきます。
Okay, that was a lot, but HoloSummer is finally starting.
みんな、今年はどんな夏にしていきたい？
Everyone, what kind of summer do you want to have?
じゃあ、フワワから。
Let's start with FUWAWA.
はい！
Yes!
え、モココも？もちろん！
Mococo too? Of course!
え、今年の夏は、ホロライブEnglish、
This summer, for hololive English,
楽しみがいっぱいあります！アツアツの夏になります！
there's a lot to look forward to! It's gonna be a hot summer!
そう、８月の頭に、ホロライブEnglish Justiceのデビューお披露目もあって、
Yes, at the start of August, there's the debut of hololive English -Justice-,
で、8月23日24日に、ホロライブEnglishサードコンサート「オールフォーワン」の2daysあります！
and on Aug 23-24, the 2-day hololive English 3rd Concert, All for One!
イエーイ！頑張るよ！
Yay! We'll do our best!
そしてね、なんかアツアツのサマーになるように、えっと、実はフワモコ
And, you know, to make it a hot summer, FUWAMOCO...
挑戦してみたいことがあります！
has something we want to try!
なになに？
What is it?
恥ずかしいんですけど
It's a little embarrassing, but...
ASMRを挑戦してみます！
We're going to try ASMR!
イエーイ！ぜひ楽しみにしてください！
Yay! Please look forward to it!
吾輩でも行けます！
I can go too!
じゃあ、次はオリーお願いします！
Okay, next up is Ollie, please!
はい！
Yes!
フワモコのおかげで覚えています！
Thanks to FUWAMOCO, I remember!
日本語はむずいから、英語で説明したいと思います！
Japanese is hard, so I'll explain in English!
We have a world tour going on,
so don't forget that! It's happening starting from summer and then we're going to go all the way.
so don't forget that! It's starting from summer, and we'll go all the way.
So make sure you guys catch everything, okay?
And with all of the announcements, I hope you guys catch up! ワラ活！
With all the announcements, I hope you guys catch up! Warakatsu!
この夏にホロライブのワールドツアー、シンクロナイズが始まります！
This summer, hololive's world tour, Synchronicity, will begin!
始まります！いろんな国を回して、
It's starting! We'll travel to many countries...
そう、ホロライブを全世界を…ね、魅力を届けるイベントです！
Yes, to deliver hololive's charm to the whole world!
よう！よう！
Yo! Yo!
で、オリー先輩…
Yeah! And Ollie-senpai...
私たちのコンサートでゲストに出演していただきますので
will be a guest performer at our concert!
頑張りましょうね！オリー先輩！
Let's do our best, Ollie-senpai!
おっす！
Ossu!
盛り上がっていきましょう！じゃあ続いてラプラス！
Let's get hyped! Next up, La+!
自分は特にないんですけど
I don't have anything special,
今年も暑いんでいっぱい汗かいて、お姉さんに「くっさ！」って言われたいと思います！
but it's hot this year, so I'll sweat a lot and have the older girls tell me I stink!
あ、じゃあマリンさん、あ、くっさー！
Oh, then from Marine... you stink!
違う！違うんじゃ！
Wrong! That's not it!
あ、虫取りで汗かいてる
Oh, you're sweating from catching bugs...
くっさー！
You stink!
キモイ！言われたよ。
Gross! She said it!
自分がカブトムシだもんな。
Because you are the beetle.
何言ってんすか！違いますよ、このツノは。
What are you talking about? These horns are different.
はい、じゃあ続いてノエちゃん！
Okay, next up is Noel-chan!
はい！いや、ホロサマ始まったということで、やっぱね、
Yes! Well, HoloSummer has started, and you know,
夏って言ったらね、すごいなんかアクティビティーな…
when you say summer, it's all about amazing activities...
感じがしますやないですか
It's a certain feeling, isn't it?
だから団長もね、あの今年の夏はいっぱい体を動かしてね
So Danchou wants to move a lot this summer
なんかみんなと一緒に楽しんでいきたいなと
and have fun with everyone.
思っておりますので、よろしくお願いします
That's what I'm thinking, so let's have a great time.
もう盛りだくさんだからね！イェーイ！
It's gonna be packed with fun! Yay!
さあ、みんなで楽しんでいこう
Well then, let's all have fun together.
夏バテだけは気をつけて
Just be careful not to get summer fatigue.
そうね。ほんとに
That's right. For real.
よーし！行きましょう！
Alright! Let's go!
はい、マリンはですね
Right, as for Marine,
うん。ごめんね、カブトムシじゃなくてクワガタだったね
Um. Sorry, it wasn't a rhino beetle, it was a stag beetle.
ごめん間違えて。ごめん、それできらってね
I'm sorry I got it wrong. Sorry.
嫌だったんだ。ごめんね。それ嫌だったんだ
You didn't like that. Sorry. You didn't like that.
ごめんね。違いますよ
I'm sorry. No, it's not like that.
はい、というわけでマリンはね、やっぱり夏と言えばマリンはね
Anyway, speaking of summer for Marine,
生誕もありますし、周年もあります
there's my birthday and my anniversary.
ま、きっとね、生誕でまたなんかライブとかするかなーみたいなムードを漂わせながら…
Well, I'm sure I'll probably do a live show for my birthday, giving off that kind of vibe...
はい、ぜひマリンの夏もお楽しみにしてください！
So please look forward to Marine's summer!
イェーイ！夏だ！
Yay! It's summer!
夏だ！夏だ！
Summer! Summer!
夏だ！ビーチだ！
Summer! Beach!
そうね。さて、ということで、まあ皆さんのね、夏の抱負というか
That's right. So, we've heard everyone's summer aspirations, so to speak.
聞けましたので、今度はリスナーさんに聞きたい
Now that we've heard them, I want to ask the listeners.
今度はリスナーさんたちはどんな夏を過ごしますか？
What kind of summer will you listeners be spending?
コメントでもいっぱい書いてください。イェーイ！
Please write a lot in the comments. Yay!
まあ、ねえ
Well, yeah, fun.
楽しい
Fun!
夏休みもね、あるから、まあ遠出するよって人
We have summer vacation, so who's going on a trip?
はーい！
Meee!
うんうんうん。あ、なるほどね
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh. I see.
え、東京に行くよって人
Uh, who's going to Tokyo?
はーい！
Meee!
はい、今「はい」と答えた皆さんは、ぜひ東京駅にあるhololive productionオフィシャルショップにもぜひお立ち寄りください
Yes, for everyone who just said "yes", please be sure to stop by the hololive production official shop at Tokyo Station.
お！お！
Oh! Oh!
はい。かわいい！
Yes. Cute!
7月17日から駅員さん風の「hololive station」衣装シリーズボリューム4が発売開始となります
From July 17th, the station attendant-style "hololive station" outfit series volume 4 will go on sale.
え、装飾に新しいサインとメッセージも追加されます
Uh, new signs and messages will also be added to the decorations.
はい、気になる方は、え、ショップ公式Xをチェックしてみてください
Yes, if you're interested, please check the official shop's X account.
いやーでもね、関西なら行くんだけどなーっていうそこのあなた！気をおとさないでください
But hey, for those of you thinking, "I'd go if it were in Kansai"... Don't be discouraged!
なんと、hololive production オフィシャルショップが大阪梅田エリアにオープンしたんです！
What?! The hololive production official shop has opened in the Osaka Umeda area!
あー！はい
Ah! Yes.
大阪梅田店のオリジナルグッズやノベルティ、店内放送など見どころ盛りだくさんです
The Osaka Umeda store is full of highlights like original goods, novelties, and in-store broadcasts.
7月25日までの期間限定で等身大パネルも設置中です
There are also life-sized standees on display for a limited time until July 25th.
船長のもあります。あるある
Marine's is there too. Ah!
はい。え、若い？今、こっちも若いよ。はい、大阪にお立ち寄りの際はぜひお立ち寄りください
Yes. Uh, young? Hey, this one's young too. Yes, please stop by when you're in Osaka.
はーい。かわいい
Okay. Cute.
ね、ファンの皆さんが素敵な夏を過ごせるように、我々もイベントだったり配信で夏を盛り上げていきましょう！
Right, so that all the fans can have a wonderful summer, let's liven things up with events and streams!
いきましょう！イェーイ！
Let's do it! Yay!
お願いします
Please do.
いや、それじゃあね、最後にみんなで「holonatsu Paradise」の開幕宣言しますか？
Well then, finally, shall we all make the opening declaration for "holonatsu Paradise"?
皆忘れてるかもしんないけど、これ開幕式なんで
You might have forgotten, but this is the opening ceremony.
そうだね
That's right.
なんか遊んでたけど。報奨もらえるあれじゃないんだよ
We were just playing around, but this isn't the part where you get a reward.
違うの？あれ？船員さんとか。いや、マリンさんないですよ
It's not? Huh? What about the crew? No, Marine doesn't have one.
あ、何だったっけな
Oh, what was it again?
ごめんごめんごめん。学力テスト…
Sorry, sorry, sorry. The academic test...
スイカかい？ スイカ食べる？みんなで
A watermelon? Should we eat it together?
食べたい！イェーイ！夏だー！
I wanna eat! Yay! It's summer!
夏だね！夏だ夏だ！
It's summer! It's summer!
熱い夏をみんなで楽しんでいきましょう！
Let's all enjoy this hot summer together!
はい！
Okay!
せーの！
Ready, set!
ホロ夏パラダイス！スタート！
Holonatsu Paradise! Start!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
hololive RESORT
ホロ夏パラダイス 開幕
Holonatsu Paradise - Grand Opening!